

About me

Date of birth: 30/08/1984

Nationality: Portuguese

Skilled and proactive Aircraft Licensed Engineer from Portugal with more than 10 years of experience in all kinds of maintenance environment. Proficient in C-checks, A-checks, Line Maintenance and all kinds of major works.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 11/06/2018 - CURRENT - Vantaa, Finland

#### B1.1 LICENSED AIRCRAFT ENGINEER/ LEAD ENGINEER

#### **Finnair Technical Services**

- Certifying Lead Engineer for Airbus A320FAM
- Perform Daily Checks and Weekly Checks on Airbus A320FAM, A330 and A350

## 11/05/2015 - 04/06/2018 - Genève, Switzerland

#### **B1.1 LICENSED AIRCRAFT ENGINEER**

#### **SR Technics Switzerland**

- Base+Line Maitenance for Easyjet Switzerland Fleet (A320FAM)
- Perform Daily and Weekly checks
- Perform P-Checks on Easyjet Switzerland aircraft
- Perform A-Checks Nightstop for Swiss aircraft (A320FAM)
- Perform Nightstop Check for other SRT customers (Iberia, TAP, etc..)
- CRS A320FAM

#### 01/10/2008 - 06/05/2015 - Lisboa, Portugal

#### LICENSED AIRCRAFT ENGINEER/ SHEET METAL WORKER

#### **TAP Maintenance & Engineering**

- Perform base maintenance in heavy aircraft, c-checks inspections as a sheet metal worker.
- Perform base maintenance in heavy aircraft, assisting in A-checks as a sheet metal worker.
- Working in Airbus A320FAM, A330/340
- Major Repairs and Modifications

- Assessment of Damage
- Structural Inspections
- Aircraft Structural Repair Mapping of A320 FAM

#### 01/10/2005 - 01/04/2006 - Lisboa, Portugal

SHOP SALESPERSON

#### Chip7

Assisting customers in computer and electronic sales

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

15/01/2007 - 25/08/2008 - Lisboa, Portugal

AIRCRAFT BASIC TRAINING COURSE PART-66 - B1.1

TAP/MTO

23/08/2010 - 13/10/2010 - Lisboa, Portugal

TYPE TRAINING COURSE OF AIRBUS A318/A319/A320/A321 (CFM56), EASA PART-66, CAT. B1.1 - THEORY

TAP/MTO

14/10/2010 - 27/10/2010 - Lisboa, Portugal

TYPE TRAINING COURSE OF AIRBUS A318/A319/A320/A321 (CFM56), EASA PART-66, CAT. B1.1 - PRACTICAL

TAP/MTO

27/03/2015 - 01/04/2015 - Budapest, Hungary

TYPE TRAINING AIRBUS A319/A320/A321 (IAE V2500) VS. AIRBUS A318/A319/A320/A321 (CFM56), EASA PART-66, CAT. B1.1 - THEORY AND PRACTICAL

Aerok Aviation Technical Training Centre Ltd.

SKILLS

# **Language Skills**

Mother Language: Portuguese

## **ENGLISH**

- ListeningC2
- ReadingC2
- SpeakingC2
- WritingC2

## **GERMAN**

- ListeningA2
- ReadingA2
- SpeakingA2
- WritingA2

#### **SPANISH**

- ListeningB1
- ReadingB1
- SpeakingA2
- WritingB2

#### **FRENCH**

- ListeningA2
- ReadingA2
- SpeakingA2
- WritingA1

# FINNISH

- ListeningA1
- ReadingA1
- SpeakingA1
- WritingA1

# **Digital Skills**

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Office
- HTML5
- CSS

Javascript

# **Driving License**

В

В1

# **Communication and interpersonal skills**

- Great team spirit
- Very good communication skills in an aircraft maintenance work environment
- I believe that a good and efficient communication plays a big role in our industry

## INTERESTS

LONG DISTANCE RUNNING

WEB DEVELOPMENT